Guide to the YMCA - Student Division Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- National Committees, Commissions, Councils, 1899-1958; Series II
  - Student Secretaries Association
    - Correspondence of W.W. Mendenhall, 1933,1934 (Box 50, Folder 736)
    - Financial documents and correspondence, 1929-1933 (Box 51, Folder 737)
    - Minutes, 1943,1944 (Box 51, Folder 738)
    - Secretaries' conferences, schools, seminars, 1913-1920 (Box 51, Folder 739)
    - Secretaries' conferences, schools, seminars, 1923-1928 (Box 51, Folder 740)
    - National Assembly of Student Secretaries, Estes Park, 1929 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Secretaries' conferences, schools, seminars, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 741)
    - Secretaries' conferences, schools, seminars, 1946-1949,n.d. (Box 51, Folder 742)
  - United Student Christian Council
    - Miscellaneous, 1945-1955 (Box 51, Folder 743)
    - USCC Organization Committee, Executive Committee; documents re. WSCF, 1946 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Topical Files: National Policy and Program Emphases, 1896-1954; Series III
  The subdivisions of this series are as follows:
  A. Disarmament
  B. Membership basis
  C. Negro student work and interracial education
  D. David R. Porter ''personal archives"
  E. Preparatory school work
  F. Recruiting and training
  G. Universal Day of Prayer for Students
  H. Voluntary study
  - Disarmament
    - Correspondence, 1921 Oct-1931 Jun-Aug (Box 52, Folder 744)
    - Correspondence, 1931 Sep (Box 52, Folder 745)
    - Correspondence, 1931 Oct 1-8 (Box 52, Folder 746)
    - Correspondence, 1931 Oct 10-Nov (Box 52, Folder 747)
    - Correspondence, 1932-1933 (Box 52, Folder 748)
    - Miscellaneous, 1921,1931-1933 (Box 52, Folder 749)
    - Miscellaneous, 1935,n.d. (Box 52, Folder 750)
    - Conferences, 1921,1931 (Box 52, Folder 751)
    - Conference, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 752)
    - Study materials, 1931-1932,n.d. (Box 52, Folder 753)
  - Membership Basis
    - Sample constitutions, 1905-1923 (Box 52, Folder 754)
    - Correspondence, 1896-1899 (Box 52, Folder 755)
    - Correspondence, 1900-1901 (Box 52, Folder 756)
    - Correspondence, 1902-1904 (Box 53, Folder 757)
    - Correspondence, 1905-1909 (Box 53, Folder 758)
    - Correspondence, 1911-1914 (Box 53, Folder 759)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1905-1910 (Box 53, Folder 760)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1911-1913 (Box 53, Folder 761)
    - Miscellaneous, 1916-1927,n.d. (Box 53, Folder 762)
    - Resolutions, 1907-l919,n.d. (Box 53, Folder 763)
    - Summary of questionnaire, 1919-1921 (Box 53, Folder 764)
    - Reports of local associations, 1899-1913,n.d. (Box 53, Folder 765)
    - Reports of local associations, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 766)
    - Basis in countries other than U.S., 1912-1920,n.d. (Box 53, Folder 767)
  - Negro Student Work and Interracial Education
    - Conferences, 1919-1936 (Box 54, Folder 768)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927-1936 (Box 54, Folder 769)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1935-1936 (Box 54, Folder 770)
    - Miscellaneous, 1937-1945,n.d. (Box 54, Folder 771)
  - David R. Porter "Personal Archives"
    - Material re: history of Student YMCA, 1908-1925 (Box 54, Folder 772)
    - Material re: history of Student YMCA, 1926-2930 (Box 54, Folder 773)
    - Material re: history of Student YMCA, 1931-1954,n.d. (Box 54, Folder 774)
  - Preparatory School Work
    - Material re: history of Student YMCA, 1908-1925 (Box 54, Folder 772)
    - Material re: history of Student YMCA, 1926-1930 (Box 54, Folder 773)
    - Material re: history of Student YMCA, 1931-1954,n.d. (Box 54, Folder 774)
    - Historical material gathered by D.R. Porter, c.1905-1913 (Box 54, Folder 775)
    - Historical material gathered by D.R. Porter, c.1914-1938 (Box 54, Folder 776)
    - Historical material gathered by D.R. Porter, c.1945-1953 (Box 54, Folder 777)
    - Historical material gathered by D.R. Porter, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 778)
    - Guides for Y-Work in the prep school, 1930-1933 (Box 55, Folder 779)
    - Lists of prep schools, 1928-1932 (Box 55, Folder 780)
    - Conferences, 1916-1918 (Box 55, Folder 781)
    - Conferences, 1919-1931 (Box 55, Folder 782)
    - National Preparatory School Committee, 1932-1943 (Box 55, Folder 783)
    - Periodical, program material, 1929-1943 (Box 55, Folder 784)
    - Reports: work in New Jersey, 1930-1932 (Box 55, Folder 785)
    - Reports: from prep schools of visiting speakers, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 786)
    - Reports: from prep schools, Blair School- Mercersburg Academy, 1930-1933 (Box 55, Folder 787)
    - Reports: from prep schools, Peddie School, Phillips-Andover Academy (Box 55, Folder 788)
    - Reports: of YMCA secretaries, 1928-1929 (Box 55, Folder 789)
    - Reports: of YMCA secretaries, 1930-1932 (Box 55, Folder 790)
    - Studies of the relation of Hi-Y work to college student work (Box 55, Folder 791)
    - Regarding Frank Bancroft, 1933 (Box 55, Folder 792)
  - Recruiting and Training
    - Miscellaneous, c.1908-1913 (Box 55, Folder 793)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1914-1915 (Box 55, Folder 794)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1915-1916 (Box 55, Folder 795)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1915-1916 (Box 56, Folder 796)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1917-1918 (Box 56, Folder 797)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1919-1922 (Box 56, Folder 798)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1923-1925 (Box 56, Folder 799)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1925-1926 (Box 56, Folder 800)
    - Miscellaneous, c.1929-1939 (Box 56, Folder 801)
    - Miscellaneous, 1941-1952,n.d. (Box 56, Folder 802)
    - Study on the Association profession, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 803)
  - Universal Day of Prayer for Students
    - Miscellaneous, 1916-1923 (Box 56, Folder 804)
    - Miscellaneous, 1945-1948 (Box 56, Folder 805)
  - Voluntary Study
    - Reports, correspondence, 1910-1911 (Box 56, Folder 806)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1912 (Box 57, Folder 807)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1913-1914 (Box 57, Folder 808)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box 57, Folder 809)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1917 (Box 57, Folder 810)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1918 (Box 57, Folder 811)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1918 (Box 57, Folder 812)
    - Reports, correspondence, 1919-1923 (Box 57, Folder 813)
    - Reports, correspondence, miscellany (Box 57, Folder 814)
    - Statistics of Bible study groups, 1907-1917 (Box 57, Folder 815)
    - Leadership training, 1916,n.d. (Box 57, Folder 816)
    - Preparatory schools, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 817)
    - Preparatory schools, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 818)
    - Groups led by A. Bruce Curry, Jr., 1923-1928 (Box 58, Folder 819)
    - Program materials, 1911-1915,n.d. (Box 58, Folder 820)
    - Program materials, 1916-1928,n.d. (Box 58, Folder 821)
  - Photographs, 1906-1933; Series VI
    A. Photographs in rolls: Arranged alphabetically by the name of the student conference to which they relate, Asilomar through Silver Bay, followed by preparatory school and miscellaneous conferences.
    B. Photographs in folders: Those related to student conferences are followed by several folders of photographs related to various organizations and topics.
    - Asilomar Conference, 1923-1932 (Box 77, Folder 995)
    - Blue Ridge Conference, 1920-1927 (Box 77, Folder 996)
    - Eagles Mere Conference, 1915-1929 (Box 77, Folder 997)
    - Estes Park Conference, 1922-1931 (Box 77, Folder 998)
    - Hollister Conference, 1923-1931 (Box 77, Folder 999)
    - Kings Mountain Conference, 1923-1933 (Box 77, Folder 1000)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1918-1930 (Box 77, Folder 1001)
    - Northfield Conference, 1927-1930 (Box 78, Folder 1002)
    - Seabeck Conference, 1922-1929 (Box 78, Folder 1003)
    - Silver Bay Conference, 1920-1925 (Box 78, Folder 1004)
    - Blairstown Prep School Conference, 1922-1928 (Box 78, Folder 1005)
    - Prep School Conferences, 1931,1932,n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1006)
    - Student Conference, 1919-1928 (Box 79, Folder 1007)
    - Miscellaneous, 1924-1931 (Box 79, Folder 1008)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1009)
    - Asilomar Conference, 1921,1929 (Box 79, Folder 1010)
    - Blue Ridge Conference, 1929 (Box 79, Folder 1011)
    - Buck Hill Falls Conference, 1930 (Box 79, Folder 1012)
    - Camp Becket Conference, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1014)
    - Chestnut Hill Conference, 1924 (Box 79, Folder 1015)
    - Bucknell University Conference, 1931 (Box 79, Folder 1013)
    - Columbia Beach Conference, 1911-1924,n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1016)
    - Eagles Mere Conference, 1929-1934 (Box 79, Folder 1017)
    - Elman Conference, 1924,n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1018)
    - Estes Park Conference, 1923-1929,n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1019)
    - Forest Park Conference, 1930,n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1020)
    - Hollister Conference, 1920,1929 (Box 79, Folder 1021)
    - Indianapolis Conference (Box 79, Folder 1022)
    - Lake Erie Conference, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 1023)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1919-1925 (Box 79, Folder 1024)
    - King's Mountain Conference, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1025)
    - Milwaukee Conference, 1926,n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1026)
    - Ministry Conference, San Anselmo, 1910 (Box 79, Folder 1027)
    - Schenectady Conference, 1922,n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1028)
    - Northfield Conference, 1906-1927 (Box 79, Folder 1029)
    - Northfield Conference, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1030)
    - Pocono Conference, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 1031)
    - Student Secretaries Conference, 1920-1922 (Box 80, Folder 1033)
    - Student Secretaries Conference, 1908,1911 (Box 80, Folder 1034)
    - SVM Convention (Des Moines, Ia.), 1920 (Box 80, Folder 1035)
    - Winslow Conference, 1919-1925 (Box 80, Folder 1036)
    - Council of Christian Association, 1925-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1037)
    - International Student Service Conference, 1912,1928 (Box 80, Folder 1038)
    - Glasgow Conference, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1039)
    - Prep School Conference (Blairstown), 1924-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1040)
    - Presidents Conference (Penn.), 1920 (Box 80, Folder 1041)
    - Y Cabinet Training Conference, 1920,1923 (Box 80, Folder 1042)
    - YM-YW Joint Conference, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1043)
    - Interseminary Conference, 1923 (Box 80, Folder 1044)
    - WSCF Conferences, 1922,1924 (Box 80, Folder 1045)
    - Local Y Cabinet Officers, l919,n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1046)
    - Local Y Activities, 1916-1928,n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1047)
    - Local Y Association Building Pictures (Box 80, Folder 1048)
    - Local Y-Association Building Pictures (Box 80, Folder 1049)
    - Secretarial Photographs (Box 80, Folder 1050)
    - Unidentified Pictures (Box 80, Folder 1051)
    - American Indian Christian Group misc. (Box 80, Folder 1052)
    - Chinese Student Conference, 1921,1931 (Box 80, Folder 1053)
    - Negro Christian Group, 1913,1929 (Box 80, Folder 1054)
    - Russian Students in Prague, 1922 (Box 80, Folder 1055)
    - Japanese European Pilgrimage Group, 1925 (Box 80, Folder 1056)
    - European Pictures, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1057)
    - Mats of Prof. G. Carver (Box 80, Folder 1058)
    - Student Summer Service, 1920-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1059)
    - Y Relief Work for Students at Kossary Blocha, Poland, 1921 (Box 80, Folder 1060)
    - Y Training School for War Workers, 1918 (Box 80, Folder 1061)
    - Student War Training, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1062)
    - Views in Northfield, Mass. (The Home of D.L. Moody) (Box 80, Folder 1063)
    - Boston Univ. School of Theol. Bangor Theol. Seminary (Box 80, Folder 1064)
    - Financial Promotion Pictures (Box 80, Folder 1065)
    - Canadian University Campuses (Box 80, Folder 1066)
    - Miscellany (incl. Students of the International Y.M.C.A. College, Springfield, MA) (Box 80, Folder 1067)
- Regional and Local Association Activities, 1886-1967; Series IV
  The first section of Series IV is arranged alphabetically by the YMCA designated geographical regions of work. Following this material are several folders of general material. The series is concluded with several oversize volumes containing records related to regional and local association activities.
  - Central Region
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1915-1918 (Box 59, Folder 822)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1919-1930 (Box 59, Folder 823)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1931-1937 (Box 59, Folder 824)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1938-1939 (Box 59, Folder 825)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1940-1942 (Box 59, Folder 826)
    - Lake Geneva Conference, 1943,1950 (Box 59, Folder 827)
    - Secretaries' meetings, working papers, 1924,1942-1955 (Box 59, Folder 828)
    - North Central area, 1941-1948 (Box 59, Folder 829)
    - Ohio area, 1945-1952 (Box 59, Folder 830)
    - Student officer conferences, 1923-1927 (Box 59, Folder 831)
    - Controversy re: E.B. Shultz, 1931 (Box 60, Folder 832)
  - Middle Atlantic Region
    - Conferences, 1914-1916 (Box 60, Folder 834)
    - Conferences, 1917-1927 (Box 60, Folder 835)
    - Conferences, 1928-1930 (Box 60, Folder 836)
    - Conferences, 1931-1938 (Box 60, Folder 837)
    - Conferences, 1939-1944 (Box 60, Folder 838)
    - Reports, minutes, 1923-1954 (Box 60, Folder 839)
  - Middle Atlantic/New England Regions
    - Silver Bay Conference, 1920-1949 (Box 60, Folder 840)
    - Presidents' Conference, 1904 (Box 60, Folder 841)
    - Presidents' Training School, 1930
    - Joint Field Council meeting, 1924 (Box 60, Folder 842)
  - Middle Atlantic Region
    - Formation of Student Christian Movement, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 843)
  - New England
    - Correspondence, miscellany, 1926-1965 (Box 60, Folder 844-848)
    - Correspondence, miscellany, 1966-1967, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 849-850)
    - Minutes, reports, 1926-1966 (Box 61, Folder 851-860)
    - Conferences, incl. at Northfield, 1886-1893 (Box 62, Folder 861)
    - Circulars, documents re. Northfield Students' Conferences, 1898-1913, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Conferences, 1911-1942, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 862-867)
    - Financial material, 1929-1966 (Box 62, Folder 868-870)
    - Work and study projects, 1961-1967 (Box 62, Folder 871-872)
    - Boston Student Workers' Council, 1927-1934 (Box 62, Folder 873)
    - Connecticut Valley World Court Committee, 1925 (Box 62, Folder 874)
    - Student YMCA study, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 875)
    - Affiliated groups, 1966-1967 (Box 63, Folder 876)
    - Associations in Maine, 1929-1930 (Box 63, Folder 877)
    - Certification application forms for Student YMCAs in Massachusetts, 1926 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Material of Wilmer Kitchen related to World's Student Christian Federation, 1929-1943 (Box 63, Folder 878-880)
  - Pacific Coast Region
    - Northwest area conference (Seabeck), 1915-1932 (Box 63, Folder 881)
    - Northwest area conference (Seabeck), 1937-1944 (Box 63, Folder 882)
    - Northwest area council meetings, etc., 1943-1945 (Box 63, Folder 883)
    - Southwest area conference (Asilomar), 1915-1930 (Box 63, Folder 884)
    - Southwest area conference (Asilomar), 1932-1940 (Box 63, Folder 885)
    - Southwest area conference (Asilomar), 1941-1950 (Box 64, Folder 886)
    - Southwest area council meetings,etc., 1916,1949-1950 (Box 64, Folder 887)
    - Reports, 1916,n.d. (Box 64, Folder 888)
  - Rocky Mountain Region
    - Estes Park Conference, 1939-1950 (Box 64, Folder 890)
    - Minutes, reports, etc., 1923-1950,n.d. (Box 64, Folder 891)
  - Southern Region
    - Blue Ridge Conference, 1915-1924 (Box 64, Folder 892)
    - Blue Ridge Conference, 1925-1930 (Box 64, Folder 393)
    - Blue Ridge Conference, 1931-1942,n.d. (Box 64, Folder 894)
    - Talladega and Berea Conferences, 1938-1953 (Box 64, Folder 895)
    - Minutes, reports, etc., 1916-1954,n.d. (Box 64, Folder 896)
  - Southwest Region
    - Hollister Conference, 1917-1932 (Box 64, Folder 897)
    - Hollister Conference, 1933-1944 (Box 65, Folder 898)
    - TAD Conference, 1950-1952 (Box 65, Folder 899)
    - Minutes, reports, etc., 1916-1953 (Box 65, Folder 900)
    - Report of discussions on a United Student Christian Movement, 1934 (Box 65, Folder 901)
  - General Material
    - Student Christian Movement of Canada - Conferences, 1918-1942 (Box 65, Folder 902)
    - Compilation of statistics related to regional and local association activities, 1895-1906 (Box 65, Folder 903)
    - General material re: regional work, 1923-1943,n.d. (Box 65, Folder 904)
    - Illustrative scrapbook relating to regional and local activities, c.1937 (Box 65, Folder 905)
    - Illustrative scrapbook relating to regional and local activities, c.1937 (Box 65, Folder 906)
    - Illustrative scrapbook relating to regional and local activities, c.1937 (Box 66, Folder 907)
    - Conference pledges, contributions, 1923 (Box 66, Folder 908)
    - Conference pledges, contributions, 1924 (Box 66, Folder 909)
    - Conference pledges, contributions, 1925 (Box 66, Folder 910)
    - Conference pledges, contributions, 1926 (Box 66, Folder 911)
    - Conference pledges, contributions, 1927-1928 (Box 66, Folder 912)
    - Income production correspondence, Pacific Coast Region, 1930-1931 (Box 66, Folder 913)
    - Southern Region reports, 1929,1930 (Box 66, Folder 914)
    - Income production correspondence, Central Region, 1932-1933 (Box 66, Folder 915)
  - Oversize Material Related to Regional and Local Association Activities
    - Volume containing conference statistics, 1896-1903 (Box Ov1)
    - Volume containing conference statistics, 1903-1909 (Box Ov2)
    - Scrapbook containing material related to conferences, pledges and Bible study, miscellaneous form letters and publications, 1904-1908 (Box Ov3)
    - Scrapbook containing material primarily related to Bible study activities at various academic institutions, 1905-1914 (Box Ov4)
    - Account book containing financial records of regional student conferences, 1910-1922 (Box Ov5)
- Publications, Studies, 1907-1954; Series V
  Following two folders of correspondence with the Association Press are topically arranged files of YMCA pamphlet publications. The YMCA studies following these pamphlets are arranged chronologically. The series is concluded with two sequences of periodical publications, those of regional SCM and YMCA organizations and those of denominational origin.
  - Correspondence between Publications Dept. (Association Press) and Student Div., 1930-1934 (Box 67, Folder 916)
  - Correspondence between Publications Dept. (Association Press) and Student Div., 1935 (Box 67, Folder 917)
  - YMCA Pamphlet Publications
    - Bible Study (Box 67, Folder 918)
    - "Character-building and Christian life" (Box 67, Folder 919)
    - "Character-building and Christian life" (Box 67, Folder 920)
    - Devotional material (Box 67, Folder 921)
    - Devotional material (Box 67, Folder 922)
    - Finance (Box 67, Folder 923)
    - Group leadership (Box 67, Folder 924)
    - Group leadership (Box 68, Folder 925)
    - Missions, mission study (Box 68, Folder 926)
    - Missions, mission study (Box 68, Folder 927)
    - Secondary school work (Box 68, Folder 928)
    - Social and political concern (Box 68, Folder 929)
    - Vocational guidance (Box 68, Folder 930)
    - Wartime issues (Box 68, Folder 931)
    - Wartime issues (Box 69, Folder 932)
    - YMCA matters (Box 69, Folder 933)
    - YMCA matters (Box 69, Folder 934)
  - YMCA Studies
    - "College problems-a study of the religious activities of college men, 1907,1909 (Box 69, Folder 935)
    - "Changing conditions in the educational world", c.l919 (Box 69, Folder 936)
    - "Research and studies II; abstracts of enterprises within the YMCA", 1930 (Box 69, Folder 937)
    - "Behavior reaction study - Factors related to student participation in Y and church work at the U. of Wisconsin", 1930 (Box 69, Folder 938)
    - "Evaluative study of counseling by student YMCA secretaries in American colleges and universities", 1947 (Box 69, Folder 939)
  - Publications and Papers of Related Groups
    - Regional SCM and YMCA Periodicals
      - Middle Atlantic region, 1934-1937 (Box 70, Folder 940-941)
      - New England region, 1930-1935 (Box 70, Folder 942-945)
      - North Central region, 1938-1940 (Box 70, Folder 946)
      - Ohio Area Student YMCA, 1938-1941 (Box 71, Folder 947-948)
      - Pacific Northwest region, 1938-1944 (Box 71, Folder 949)
      - Rocky Mountain region, 1935-1938 (Box 71, Folder 950-952)
      - Southern region, 1937-1945 (Box 71, Folder 953)
      - Southwest region, 1937-1939 (Box 71, Folder 954)
      - Southwest region, 1940-1945 (Box 72, Folder 955-957)
    - Denominational Publications
      - News Letter for Workers Among Students, 1928-1933 (Box 72, Folder 958)
      - News Letter of the Student Pilgrim Fellowship, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 959)
      - Student Life Notes, 1939-1940 (Box 72, Folder 960)
      - Student Life Notes, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 961)
      - Student Life Notes, 1942 (Box 72, Folder 962)
      - Student Life Notes, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 963)
      - Student Work Bulletin, 1935-1936 (Box 73, Folder 964)
      - Student Work Bulletin, 1937 (Box 73, Folder 965)
      - Student Work Bulletin, 1938,1941 (Box 73, Folder 966)
      - Values, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 967)
      - Youth, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 968)
      - Student Service Bulletin, 1940-1942 (Box 73, Folder 969)
      - Student Service Bulletin, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 970)
      - American Lutheran Student, 1940-1941 (Box 73, Folder 971)
      - Student Welfare Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 972)
      - Student Service Commission, 1944 (Box 74, Folder 973)
      - Wesley Foundation Bulletin, 1933-1934 (Box 74, Folder 974)
      - Wesley Foundation Bulletin, 1935 (Box 74, Folder 975)
      - Wesley Foundation Bulletin, 1936 (Box 74, Folder 976)
      - Wesley Foundation Bulletin, 1937 (Box 74, Folder 977)
      - Wesley Foundation Bulletin, 1938 (Box 74, Folder 978)
      - Wesley Foundation Bulletin, 1939 (Box 75, Folder 979)
      - Methodist Student Bulletin, 1940-1941 (Box 75, Folder 980)
      - Methodist Student Bulletin, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 981)
      - Methodist Student Bulletin, 1943 (Box 75, Folder 982)
      - Methodist Student Bulletin, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 983)
      - News Bulletin, 1931-1932, 1934-1937 (Box 75, Folder 984)
      - Presbyterian Student, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 985)
      - Presbyterian Student, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 987)
      - Presbyterian Student, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 988)
      - Various, 1936-1944 (Box 76, Folder 989)
      - The Church Review, 1940-1941 (Box 76, Folder 990)
      - The Church Review, 1942-1945 (Box 76, Folder 991)
      - Division of College Work Bulletin, 1941-1945 (Box 76, Folder 992)
      - American Unitarian Youth, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 993)
      - Unitarian College Centers Bulletin, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 994)
    - National Intercollegiate Christian Council
      - SPAN-Student Public Affairs News, 1945-1954 (Box 76, Folder 994)
- Addendum - 2010, 1910-1956; Series VII
  - Student work during World War II
    See also Record Group No. 99, Archives of the War Emergency Council on Student Christian Work
    - Plans for wartime expansion of YMCA student work, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Consultative Conference on War-Time Plans of the Student YMCA, Chicago, 1943 Mar (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Wartime Program Supplement, National Council Bulletin, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Army and Navy Department Committee minutes, recommendations, 1944 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Literature Committee of Army and Navy Department, 1943-1944 (Box 87, Folder 5-6)
    - Seminars on Personal Counseling on Wartime Problems, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Service Men's Christian League, 1943-1946 (Box 87, Folder 8-9)
    - Program Bulletin issued by Army and Navy Department, 1943-1944 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - YMCA-USO activities, 1943 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
    - YMCA-USO literature, ca. 1943-1944 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Girls Service Organization, 1943 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      "The function of the Girls Service Organization is to provide wholesome recreational opportunities for service men in the form of dnaces, parties, informal gatherings, and special entertainment."